[
  {
    "question": "The fat boy likes climbing trees. （改成一般疑问句）",
    "answers": ["Does the fat boy like climbing trees?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "I study at home.（改为一般疑问句）",
    "answers": ["Do you study at home?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The boy doesn't have a key ring.（改为肯定句）",
    "answers": ["The boy has a key ring."]
  },
  {
    "question": "She works \"in the hospital\".（对画线部分提问）",
    "answers": ["Where does she work?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Are they watching TV?（作否定回答）",
    "answers": ["No, they aren't.", "No, they are not."]
  },
  {
    "question": "My father is \"a bank clerk\".（对画线部分提问）",
    "answers": [
      "What is your father's job?",
      "What's your father's job?",
      "What does your father do?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "That tall man is \"Jack\". (划线部分提问) ",
    "answers": ["Who's that tall man?", "Who is that tall man?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The girl \"in the short black dress\" can dance very well. (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": ["Which girl can dance well?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "There are some desks and chairs in the classroom. (改成否定句)",
    "answers": [
      "There are not any desks or chairs in the classroom.",
      "There aren't any desks or chairs in the classroom."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There are no classrooms in the forest. （意思不变，另写一句)",
    "answers": ["There are not any classrooms in the forest."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the matter? （意思不变，另写一句）",
    "answers": ["What is wrong?", "What's wrong?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr Black is \"a teacher from the UK\". (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": ["What does My Black do?", "What is Mr. Black's job?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "There are a lot of books in the library. (改成否定句)",
    "answers": ["There aren't many books in the library."]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is \"a big clothes shop\" on Nanjing Road. (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": ["What is on Nanjing Road?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "I want \"a\" bottle of water. (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": ["How many bottles of water do you want?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "I want \"a bottle of\" water. (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": ["How much water do you want?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How much is the loaf of bread? （改为复数）",
    "answers": ["How much are the loaves of bread?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "We can \"take the school bus\" to Century Park? (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": ["How can you go to Century Park?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Danny is riding the bicycle \"near the fountain\". (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": ["Where is Danny riding the bicycle?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Peter is \"showing his photos\". (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": ["What is Peter doing?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How's the weather in spring? (改为同义句)",
    "answers": [
      "What's the weather like in spring?",
      "What is the weather like in spring?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's sunny. （改为同义句）",
    "answers": ["It's a sunny day", "It's fine."]
  },
  {
    "question": "How are you doing? （改为同义句）",
    "answers": ["How are you?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "I like sunny and hot days best. (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": ["What weather do you like best?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The weather in April is warm and wet in Shanghai. （改成否定句，句意不变）",
    "answers": ["The weather in April isn't cool or dry in Shanghai."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Grace is walking to school now. （改成同义句）",
    "answers": ["Grace is going to school on foot now."]
  },
  {
    "question": "The pig lives \"in a pen\". (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": ["Where does the pig live?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The mouse has small and sharp teeth. （改成否定句，句意不变）",
    "answers": ["The mouse doesn't have big or blunt teeth."]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is \"a bag of\" corn on the floor. (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": ["How much corn is there on the floor?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jill has \"five\" loaves of bread. (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": ["How many loaves of bread does Jill have?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The farmer is feeding his pig. (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": ["What is the farmer doing?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'd like a large bag of corn. （改成一般疑问句）",
    "answers": ["Would you like a large bag of corn?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Peter is playing football in the playground. (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": [
      "What's Peter doing in the playground?",
      "What is Peter doing in the playground?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When's Christmas? （按实际情况回答）",
    "answers": ["It's in December"]
  },
  {
    "question": "We often make phone calls to each other. （一般疑问句，肯定回答）",
    "answers": ["Do you often make phone calls to each other?Yes, we do."]
  },
  {
    "question": "He studies in a high school(改成现在进行时态) Now",
    "answers": [
      "he is studying in a high school.",
      "He is studying in a high school."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "They are watching TV in the living room. （一般疑问句，肯定回答）",
    "answers": ["Are they watching TV in the living room?Yes, they are."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen! The birds are \"singing\" in the tree. (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": ["What are the birds doing in the tree?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "\"Superdog\" feels tired. (写出一句特殊疑问句)",
    "answers": ["Who feels tired?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "My friend has \"a tin of cola\" for the class party. (划线部分提问)",
    "answers": ["What does your friend have for the class party? "]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dolly is good at speaking English.(句意不变，转换句型)",
    "answers": ["Dolly can speak English well."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tracy walks to the park every week.(句意不变，转换句型)",
    "answers": ["Tracy goes to the park on foot every week."]
  },
  {
    "question": "My father goes to work by feet.(判断句子对错，有错的改在横线上。)",
    "answers": ["on foot"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The boy put some ice cream on the bread. (判断句子对错，有错的改在横线上。)",
    "answers": ["puts"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Old macdonalds farm is big its near our school(正确抄写句子，注意大小写和标点符号)",
    "answers": ["Old MacDonald's farm is big. It's near our school."]
  },
  {
    "question": "用括号（）中所给单词的正确形式填空，答案用空格分隔：",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "There (be) some restaurants and a post office around my home.",
    "answers": ["are"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Touch the (sweater)  ---Oh, they‘re soft and warm.",
    "answers": ["sweaters"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't make a noise! The babies (sleep).",
    "answers": ["are sleeping"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who (stand) over there now?",
    "answers": ["is standing"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kitty (like) (paint). Look! She (paint).",
    "answers": ["likes painting is painting"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's 12 o'clock. The students (have) lunch.",
    "answers": ["are having"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't talk here. Grandparents (sleep).",
    "answers": ["are sleeping"]
  },
  {
    "question": "I have a pet.(it) tail is long.",
    "answers": ["Its"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Supergirl doesn't like (write), so she isn't good at (write).",
    "answers": ["writing writing"]
  },
  {
    "question": "He (want) to (drink) some water.",
    "answers": ["wants drink"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Can Mary (watch) TV every evening? No, she can't.",
    "answers": ["watch"]
  },
  {
    "question": "介词填空，答案用空格分隔：",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "() Christmas, I get many presents () my parents.",
    "answers": ["At from"]
  },
  {
    "question": "My little brother can count () one () one hundred.",
    "answers": ["from to"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Monkeys can swing () their tails.",
    "answers": ["with"]
  },
  {
    "question": "These bottles () water are for you.",
    "answers": ["of"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Please draw a map () your school.",
    "answers": ["of"]
  },
  {
    "question": "首字母填空, 判断正误，答案用空格分隔：",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello, everyone! I l() on Green Street. It is not busy. There is a school on it.",
    "answers": ["live"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's not far a() from my home. So I walk to school w() my classmates every day.",
    "answers": ["away with"]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is a bus stop in front of the school gate. Many people t() a bus there.My mother takes a bus at this bus stop too.",
    "answers": ["take"]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is a small park near the school. I can see many trees and flowers there. People can walk, dance and fly a kite in it. ",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is a() a mountain in the park. People like climbing the mountain in the morning. How happy they are!",
    "answers": ["also"]
  },
  {
    "question": "I go to school by bus. 判断正误(T/F)",
    "answers": ["F", "f"]
  },
  {
    "question": "首字母填空, 判断正误，答案用空格分隔：",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's Saturday tomorrow. We are going to watch a football match. It's between a Japanese team and a C() team.",
    "answers": ["Chinese"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The football match is going to be at f() o'clock in the afternoon.",
    "answers": ["four"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Our teachers Mr Li and Mr Wang are going to watch the football match w() us.",
    "answers": ["with"]
  },
  {
    "question": "We are going there on f().",
    "answers": ["foot"]
  },
  {
    "question": "We can come b() at about six in the evening.",
    "answers": ["back"]
  },
  {
    "question": "判断正误，用T/F表示. <Great Time>",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Time: 11:00 AM; Date: Oct.5th; Day:Wednesday;",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Place: Garden Park (No. 8, Garden Road); Age: 14-18",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Activities: 1. Get to know new friends; 2. Have a BBQ; 3. Play some games",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contact Person: Mandy Green Telephone number: 56784321",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "1. Great Time is on the fifth of October",
    "answers": ["T"]
  },
  {
    "question": "2. Great Time is in the evening",
    "answers": ["F"]
  },
  {
    "question": "3. Young people can know new friends in Great Time",
    "answers": ["T"]
  },
  {
    "question": "4. There is no food for Great Time",
    "answers": ["F"]
  },
  {
    "question": "5. Mandy Green's phone number is 56784321",
    "answers": ["T"]
  },
  {
    "question": "6. You are ten years old. You can't go to Great Time.",
    "answers": ["T"]
  },
  {
    "question": "判断正误，用T/F表示.",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Water is important to people, animals and plants. But water pollution is very serious in China and some other countries. People throw a lot of rubbish into the river. The water in the river becomes dirty and smelly. Fish, frogs, shrimps and many plants can't live in it. People can't drink the water from the river or water the plants. That's terrible. How can we protect our water resource?",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Water pollution is very serious in China.",
    "answers": ["T"]
  },
  {
    "question": "首字母填空, 判断正误，答案用空格分隔：",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ben Webb is going to be eleven years old tomorrow. Ben's mother is going to give a b() party to him.",
    "answers": ["big"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Now all the family members are b() now. Mrs Webb is making a birthday cake.",
    "answers": ["busy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ben and his sister help to c() the house.",
    "answers": ["clean"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Now Mr Webb is talking w() Mrs Webb.",
    "answers": ["with"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr Webb: Can I help you, dear?",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mrs Webb: Yes. Can you go s() now?",
    "answers": ["shopping"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr Webb: Sure.",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mrs Webb: Is there any m() in the fridge?",
    "answers": ["meat"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr Webb：No there isn't.",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mrs Webb: Buy some beef and twenty chicken legs. Is there any orange juice?",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "根据上文回答：Is there any beef in the fridge?",
    "answers": ["No, there isn't.", "No, there is not."]
  },
  {
    "question": "根据表格中提供的信息，在横线上回答问题<A picnic>",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Date: Friday, June 9th; Time:11 o'clock in the morning",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Place: Shanghai Zoo; Participants: Students of Grade 5;",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Food for lunch:Bring the food you like; Activities: Play ball games",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "1.Is it Friday?",
    "answers": ["Yes, it is."]
  },
  {
    "question": "2.Is the picnic in the afternoon?",
    "answers": ["No, it isn't.", "No, it is not."]
  },
  {
    "question": "3.Where are the students going?",
    "answers": ["They are going to Shanghai Zoo."]
  },
  {
    "question": "4.Can they eat and play there?",
    "answers": ["Yes, they can."]
  },
  {
    "question": "5.Who can have a picnic on that day?",
    "answers": ["Students of Grade 5."]
  },
  {
    "question": "写出动词的现在分词形式",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "work",
    "answers": ["working"]
  },
  {
    "question": "sit",
    "answers": ["sitting"]
  },
  {
    "question": "drop",
    "answers": ["dropping"]
  },
  {
    "question": "判断划线部分发音，用T/F表示",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "\"E\"leven tw\"e\"lve",
    "answers": ["F"]
  },
  {
    "question": "dr\"aw\" f\"our\"teen",
    "answers": ["T"]
  },
  {
    "question": "阅读信息，填写英语单词，完成短文（字数不限）",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Name: Eddie; Age: Eleven; Class: Class Four, Grade Four;",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Student number: 22; Hobby: reading and skating;",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Address: No.12, Garden Road; Phone number: 5669432;",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello, I'm Eddie. I am a pupil from ().",
    "answers": ["Class Four, Grade Four"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the class, my number is ().",
    "answers": ["22"]
  },
  {
    "question": "I love () very much. I live at No.12, on Garden Road.",
    "answers": ["reading and skating"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you want to see me, please dial 5669432. Please remember my (). Maybe we can be friends.",
    "answers": ["Phone Number", "Phone number", "phone number"]
  },
  {
    "question": "首字母填词并回答问题",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Human and pets b() have feelings.",
    "answers": ["both"]
  },
  {
    "question": "We laugh a() smile to show that we are happy. ",
    "answers": ["and"]
  },
  {
    "question": "But dogs wag tails to tell us they f() happy. ",
    "answers": ["feel"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you see cats attack or bite, that shows they are v() angry.",
    "answers": ["very"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your pets and you can be friends if you l() and understand e() other.",
    "answers": ["love each"]
  },
  {
    "question": "1.Do human and pets have feeling?",
    "answers": ["Yes, they do."]
  },
  {
    "question": "2.What do dogs do when they are happy?",
    "answers": ["Wag tails"]
  },
  {
    "question": "3.Why are pets friendly to us? Because ()",
    "answers": ["we love and understand each other"]
  },
  {
    "question": "4.How can we know the cats are angry?",
    "answers": ["Attack or bite."]
  },
  {
    "question": "圈出错误处，把正确答案写在横线上",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "How much milk are there in the bottle?",
    "answers": ["is"]
  },
  {
    "question": "He usually go to the bookstore with his mother.",
    "answers": ["goes"]
  }
]
